🎶
"What's your name?"
A simple question but my answer’s really never the same
Maybe ask again tomorrow but “no promises” I have to disclaim
Each decision I make, I wish I could erase
Yet you expect me to not feel like I’m a basket case?
My reflection in the screen makes distortions of my face
And I can only focus on the worst case
Tell me, what’s my name?
Is it one or the other, I’ll never know it now
Someone just figure it out for me somehow,
I don’t wanna feel this shame
But the way things are going,
I might always be the same
Let me clear my brain
‘Cause my head keeps on spinning long as I complain
🎶
“What’s your name?”
I stare at blank pages tryna figure out which person to blame
Every time I make it different,
feels like somehow it’s going to pay
What’s my name?
Is there even one that fits me?
My identity is never explained
What’s in a name?
Does it matter now or ever if the whole world’s gone up in flames?
🎶
Tell me, what’s my name?
Is it one or the other, I’ll never know it now
Someone just figure it out for me somehow,
I don’t wanna feel this pain
But the way things are going,
I might always be the same
Choices are my bane
I can tell that my effort would
all
be
in
vein.
🎶
Tell me, what’s my name?
Is it one or the other, I’ll never know it now
Someone just figure it out for me somehow,
I don’t wanna feel this shame
But the way things are going,
I might always be the same
Let me clear my brain
‘Cause my head keeps on spinning long as
I
complain!
🎶